CELSO KLOSOSKI

E-mail: celsoh.klososki@gmail.com

Phone: (778) 251-3584

Address: 1334 East 12th Avenue

Vancouver, BC - V5N 1Z9

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Well-organized administrative assistant bringing excellent multitasking abilities developed over two years of administration experience and over three years of customer service experience. A very good team-player with expertise to learn quickly. Responsible, punctual and productive professional when working with little to no supervision.

SKILLS

- Friendly, reliable, organized.
- Good command of English.
- Portuguese Native-speaker.
- Spreadsheet Management.
- Troubleshoot.
- Multitasking.
- Teamwork.
- Microsoft Office.
- Office administration.
- Project Management.
- HTML.
- CSS.
- JavaScript.
- SQL.
- UI/UX.
- Microsoft Visio.
- Web Development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Retail Supervisor

Canadian Tire | Nov 2020 - Present

- Train and guide associates to maximize team performance.
- Coordinate merchandising of new products, including displays, signage and sales enablement.
- Assist customers by answering questions and fulfilling requests.
- Keep merchandise fresh by monitoring use of proper stock rotation procedures and setting up promotions to move out aging products.

Sales Associate

Canadian Tire | Feb 2019 - Oct 2020

- Provide exceptional customer service to foster client loyalty and satisfaction.
- Manage customer relations and customer service through daily communication and interaction.
- Communicate effectively with co-workers to maintain high-quality service.
- Maintain organized, presentable merchandise to drive continuous sales.

Administrative Assistant

ViajarMais Turismo & Intercâmbio | Jan 2017 - Dec 2018

- Managed payroll, transactions, invoicing and budgeting to decrease financial inconsistencies.
- Improved customer information collection and sales recordkeeping accuracy by implementing an organization software to keep the data organized.
- Responsible for assistance and visa application analysis.
- Daily interaction with customers and suppliers by email, phone and meetings.
- Assisted executive leaders in decision-making procedures by creating monthly reports to advise leaders on corrective actions and process improvements.

EDUCATION HIGHLIGHTS

British Columbia Institute of Technology - Vancouver, BC Applied Web Development | Mar2019 - Present

Greystone College - Vancouver, BCCustomer Service Diploma | Jan 2019 - Dec 2019

FAE Business School - Curitiba, Brazil

Production Engineering | Jan 2018 - Dec 2018

Pontificia Universidade Católica do Paraná - Curitiba, Brazil Mechatronics Engineering | Jan 2011 - Dec 2017